good, good, good flower
in
by
fool
wooo
ni
What a surprise!
No, it's not.
Dracula's laundry horseradish. I put it between the ground clothes.
Why did I put my ground clothes in there?
I'm off!
It was sweet potatoes.
That's great!
Welcome!
Good luck!
Hello, everyone!
What a color!
It's light blue.
Thank you very much.
Today is Halloween.
I'm sorry to take away your big day.
I'm sorry to have taken away your big day.
I'm sorry for taking away your big day, but...
Last year, I probably couldn't do it.
I didn't have a chance to do it last year.
I'm so happy that we could hold the birthday event this year.
I'm very happy that we were able to hold it this year.
Thank you very much.
Today, we have a guest.
I would like to call on you today because you have kindly come here.
I'd like to call out the doggie guests. Please come in.
I'm sorry to disturb you.
Please come in.
Take your time.
Take your time. Thank you.
Thank you for staying with us until the end of the day.
I look forward to working with you.
Now I would like to go to the first project.
The first project is the quiz Lilicao!
Lilikao! What is that?
As the title says, it's a quiz.
Everyone, all the members of ONE, you like me a lot, don't you?
I'm in a bit of a quandary, but I thought I'd try to decide who likes me the most.
Since we're at this point, I thought it would be easier to decide.
I think it would be easier to decide.
It seems like everyone likes Jerrica.
I'm in trouble. If you're in trouble, that's fine.
I'm sorry, I really am.
I'd like to see some happy frames.
I'm just saying that you're all very motivated.
I don't know what to do.
May I ask you to sit down?
My past asha will be here.
So some of those asha will be enlarged and appear here.
You will be asked to guess what song this Asha is.
You mean when is this Asha?
The successive generations.
Well, her knees are a little red, so it's after the assembly.
Is it Stopy? Something like that.
Is that what you mean?
Our knees are always red when we sit down.
Then we stand up.
The one with the most correct answers will win.
Is there something in it for me?
Yes, there is.
Oh, my God.
I have a kiss for you.
Would you like to take advantage of it yourself?
I'll do it 100 times behind your back.
I don't want it.
I'm not going to do it here.
Sorry. I'll just stand here and wipe it off.
Let me sanitize it and then we'll do it.
Okay.
So, ladies and gentlemen.
I would like to ask you all to work your way up to the middle of the room.
Now, here is the first question.
Go ahead.
Become famous.
Yes. 7 points!
Seven points!
Melaniezer, this is for you.
Amazing!
You've been here recently.
All dressed, sir.
Oh, this one...
Here, too?
The next question is...
Uh, excuse me. Continue.
Go ahead.
Cat punch.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
I know what this is.
Seven points!
If I say it's a cute problem, can I ask you to stay here with me, so I can get a good look at it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What's with the face?What kind of face is this?
Mirin, Urchoko.
What? What?
Seven.
What?
Well, my impression of the bread.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
I thought you wouldn't recognize it.
Here's the next question.
You can tell by the nails, can't you, ladies and gentlemen?
Nail maniacs!
Shanim Ninkir's right hand.
But it's not the nails, it's the photo.
Oh, wow, that way.
It's a film, right?
Well, if it's not film...
I understand! You know, I tell you every day.
"You changed your nails.
She looks at my nails.
Here's the fifth question.
Oh, I know this one!
Luka!
Papioca Milichi's.
Five.
Correct.
Wow, that's a little faster than I thought.
But I'm pretty sure they're all the same.
The same.
They're different colors.
Pasqui, too. Say "papioca.
I know what it is.
I know what you mean.
Now get ready for this.
Last problem.
This is...
Should I?
The best face.
How do you know?
I love this face, Hazuki.
I could tell by your face.
It's so frustrating.
I'm so frustrated.
I'm lying.
About 3 points now.
I'm sure you'll get a lot more than that.
What?
Wait a minute.
It's so frustrating. It's really frustrating.
It's frustrating. You're lying.
You mean you're happy?
You know, Hatsuki was smiling at me.
He was grinning.
She said she was frustrated, frustrated.
See?
Was he smiling? Just now.
He's laughing so hard.
He was already crying.
He's coming closer.
Can I ask you to look into his eyes?
Are you disappointed?
Plus 3 points!
I'm frustrated.
I'm so frustrated.
She lied to you, didn't she?
But I still wondered what the points were for. I mean, you don't want to sell points cheap, do you?
You don't want to sell points cheap, do you?
Wait a minute.
That's a lot.
Well done.
I got 3 points each.
So, the winner goes to Adeka Michi!
Congratulations!
Sap-sap-sap.
Yasuri yasuri.
Congratulations!
I'm so happy.
Are you happy?
Are you lying? Are you okay?
I'm gonna get points for that. Are you okay with that?
Okay, so, I'm going to ask you to give me a little kiss behind the scenes.
Save your money.
I'll save up.
That's all for now, this is Quiz Lilicao!
Everyone, you put "4th place start" in the box, don't you?
Then, you compete for the number of seconds until you find "〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜".
Oh, is that it?
Please do it as fast as you can.
Here it is. This way.
100 points for first place, 4 points for second place, 3 points for third place, 2 points for fourth place, and 1 point for fifth place.
Who's thick?
This is my decision, so don't complain too much.
Oh, really?
Ririka first.
Yes, it is.
Interesting, interesting.
Then I guess it's Lilika's.
Yo, let's start!Let's get started!
Can't you put your hand in suddenly?
Lyrica.
What's this?
I can really feel it.
Oh, no, no, no, no. We don't have much time.
Well, when do you use it?
When it's important?
Yeah, when it's important.
Oh, it's not a koppen.
Yes, it is. When it's important.
I'll do the Coppen at the important time.
Sure.
Please elaborate in detail.
What kind of seal?
What kind?
More... letters.
Find some letters.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm writing letters.
A child's seal?
Do I have to answer in such detail?
It's a challenge for a 7 year old. Let's start preparing!
konnyaku
You're early.
I could tell even before I touched it. I could smell it the moment I came here.
It smelled so bad.
It smells really bad.
This was a bit of a mistake.
I'm in first place. I'm number one.
I can see that.
They prepared something really good for us.
You prepared it?
Yes, I did. Congratulations.
I like it.
It's frustrating.
There are products that I can't quite afford.
It's strange.
Such a lot of candy!
I love it.
Amazing.
Have you forgotten your hearts?
I knew you've all made a lot of money.
I thought that since you've already made a lot of money, you wouldn't be pleased with the donation or the brand name goods.
So, we decided to give them sweets.
Ririko, I wish I had gotten you something brand new.
Hmm?
Staff, brand-name goods.
I'm sorry.
But there's a lot of stuff in here.
They put so much in!
Looks delicious.
Oh, you don't mind, do you?
You can share it later.
What? By myself?
Can I share?
Can I split it with you?
And I just roughly put myself in there.
Can I share?
Okay, now, don't you...
Turn around.
Okay, I got it.
Now, listen up.
On one.
Yoi, Don!
AUWAKAKU HAKARI
Thank you very much. We've finished the first part.
How was it?
I was nervous. But everyone made me laugh a lot and it was a warm event.
Thank you very much.
Yamanote line game until the balloon breaks.
The first question was, "What is your favorite thing about Wasta?
Cute.
Star.
Slightly gentle.
Slightly easy.
Fun.
Oriko.
Hey, staff.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
We should have done this project.
It's still growing.
Let's get started.
Eh, body.
Tokai On Air marinade
Live performance is fun!
They are polite.
Cat ears look good on you.
Cute costumes!
The place with Ririka
She's smart
Kind! Kind!
Oh, no! Funny!
As if?
You're late.
You know, I've got two of those headgear.
I wanted two, for the sake of the picture.I wanted two of them, picture-wise.
Two people can throw up once again.
Ahhh...
Really?
Wait a minute.
You've got to be kidding me.
A melody that echoes around the world to this day.
That's what it is, isn't it?
So many hearts, so many hearts.
Okay, the center event is over.
I was able to sing my solo songs in both parts of the event.
I was also able to do some projects I wanted to do, so I'm happy.
I had costumes made for today's event.
It was made with light blue, my member's color.
The overall look of the outfit is very dress-like and cute.
I thought of the shape and design of the outfit from scratch, so if you like it, please feel free to click the good button!
If you like it, please click the "Good" button!
Please subscribe to my channel!
That's all for now, it was a lot of fun!
Thank you very much!
Great job!
I would like to story this one now.
Yay! I'm so happy.
What do you guys like?
Are you with me?
Yes, I am.
Just for today?
Just today.
Oh, you want me to expose everything in such a short time?
Yes, I'm going to be in close contact with you from this time until I return home on the Shinkansen.
Oh, it's scary.
I'm scared.
Nice to meet you.
Excuse me.
The next one is for people.
In the meantime, I'd like to eat my lunch.
With my parents.
Oh, parents...
Oh, there was a temper
Excuse me
Oh, katsudon.
What would you like to eat?
Yay! I don't care what you want!
Oh, no, Hajiki-chan, I chose what you like best.
You sure?
Okay, umm...
I'll go with tempura.
End of close call.
I will be joining the company.
Pleased to meet you.
Screen attached.
I've never seen this guy before.
The screen is on.
It's a bit of a mess on my costume.
I think I'm going to have to put my top on from the front.
Can I say something funny?
Go ahead.
This chair folds up.
But if you turn it backwards, it raises up.
Please be careful.
I laughed at that earlier.
I've been doing that a lot since a few minutes ago.
You're doing it?
I'm surprised.
I told you earlier.
Bon appétit.
Amazing.
Ten. Tendon.
Tendon.
Let's eat!
Shishito Challenge!
This shishito is a dish that Ms. Misato Matsuda of a certain idol group
Ms. Misato Matsuda of an idol group has a technique that when she eats shishito, she is sure to get a spicy one.
I have never hit it yet.
I would like to try the shishito challenge!
I'll try it!
It's so delicious!
Chiharu roll
Here's what I just said. Now what did I say?
Yes, it was totally fine. This is Sakamoto Tsurugi at the end of the second part!
I'm the same person as before.
I'm still the same person I was before, but in the second part, there were a few people who were oohing and aahing, which made me want to congratulate them so much.
They were all so cute, and I was so grateful to them for coming to see me.
Well then...
I think we should talk a little bit more. Do you have anything to talk about? After all, we're in such close contact.
I'm sure we'll talk about things we wouldn't normally get to hear.
I'm sure the person who edits this camera thinks it would be good to have something like that.
What kind of questions do you ask when you are in close contact with people?
I don't think so. The staff wants to know what they're going to ask.
Let's open a Miss... No, just now...
I had a Ponte chocolate.
Which one do you like best?
The one I like best...
If it's a doughnut...If it's doughnuts.
Pontering's chocolate is my favorite.
So, not doughnuts?
Doughnuts.
Not the regular kind, the ones with the name like "Pop Pop Pop".
I like the donuts with names like Pop Pop Pop the best.
Thank you very much.
Are you sure we're sticking together? I'm starting to worry about you.
Mmmm.
They're consistently delicious.
Well, please give me three minutes.
Three minutes, please.
Yes, ma'am.
Now...
Three minutes.
I think this is probably where the most people are crying.
I'm going to go see them cry. I'll try not to cry.
Okay, I'm gonna get in the elevator.
Well, everyone.
Thank you so much for coming today.
I'm the last one to put out a photo book, and I'm so happy that the five of us could do it together.
And I am so happy that so many of you came.
I am very happy to be here in Kobe for the last time.
Thank you all for coming.
I will do my best for the concert on the 25th.
Thank you very much.
Well, the last benefit event is over.
I was so excited to think that this was the last one, but...
I don't have much vocabulary, but there were so many people who came to the event.
I am so happy that so many people came and came up with so many different poses.
I'm very happy that they came up with so many different poses, and I'm glad that they did.
But we did a lot of weird poses from the back of the photo book, and some of them were the worst poses because they were the last.
We also did a lot of worst poses because it was the last show, so we did a lot of worst poses.
It was a lot of fun, so I thought I could do my best for the live performance.
Many of the people who came today said they would go on the 25th, so I will do my best to find them from the stage.
I will do my best to find them from the stage.
Ah!
First of all, yes.
Thank you for watching.
[Hajime Shacho ending]
Oh, I'm scared. I should have done this project.
I don't know.
Is he talking?